And this is the hotel you how we can recreate application that is no longer available, but I found this is actually very useful, especially for us in investigations.
So this extension shows when it was published, even more of who is the source of the article or paste the content you already think.
And this is the accuracy and there is a more information that is not here.
There is a source code to see the source because you can use CRX, you use source, you can open the normal stuff and we can even allow it or try to replicate it.
And after that, I'll open a cursor and I can paste the Chrome Web Store.
This is a Chrome extension that shows location date, may you analyze it for me.
All right, we see consider activity maintain alternatives for developers use model Chrome extension API, the implementation methods.
I want to create a model version of this extension and I'll add agent, create a model version of this extension.
It will be our first task.
It will be a small extension, but still very useful.
We don't need to publish it on the Chrome Web Store because what I want is just to use an extension.
In my way, maybe extend it a little bit just for my private investigations.
So I can click Faucely from my crop extensions and then see whenever this is pop, whenever this will be catered.
So this will help me out.
And I will use this article as a balance.
Okay, so it's creating.
Let me see the color key.
We see it pop up on the face.
Then you can open it up to see the changes.
Okay, let me check the model first, there is some.
It's creating some icon.
So we have to add it.
It's creating now a directory of icons and presets.
So we will obviously have to change because we cannot use it, but we can recreate it in our way.
This creating icon generated for readme.
So we'll do a little bit like another one for icons.
So now it's preparing a mark done file, which is the list of the instructions that we can use for that extension.
As you can see, the extension is ready to use once you generate the icon files.
I can make it create some placeholder icons.
Just for a quick testing, I'll make a workaround with default icons.
First, let the whole next extension.
So I'll ask it.
We still have a gig now.
The things that will be prepared.
I think actually this gig now installation was the option, music thing tool.
We can generate its own.
This is even that we can up in our web browser.
So even if I go here and go to icons, I can generate there's a riff of icon generator
that we can use, but it's okay.
So if I see create, place for the icons, we'll do a script file.
So now when I have icon generator, I can open this.
They can ruin a file explorer, open it here.
They can generate the icons.
I can download it.
We see when it's downloaded, create some kind of possibility.
If I go now to Chrome extension to my sorry for the don't date of icons now.
And then after that, when the extension is loaded, I can just try and use a lot of impact.
Chrome extension or don't data file.
And we see already it's here.
And now we'll just see here and I will go to the address.
And I will say find publication data.
Okay, so it's using like open graph metadata.
But I want to make it more simple.
So I'll open it like hacking news.
It's like I may be found and I won't after the first click to reveal that it tries to find publication data.
And I want to remove the top line.
So the first thing I'll ask is a new agent.
Remove the name of the emails.
And the application date finder.
And manifest this should have an aim for general data.
You move about link with version.
And when I press a Chrome extension icon while on article, it should automatically search.
So the bottom and application date should fire automatically when pressed.
All right.
I could probably split it into multiple tasks for new agents.
But I think it will be all right because this is more extension showing the possibilities that you can recreate icons.
All right.
As we can see all judges are complete and there are no inter errors.
I'll go to extension our reload.
We didn't see any mistakes.
So now if I press L, we see publication data.
Okay, let's try another one.
I will go maybe this and this.
This is now the loss and I'll open it.
It shows November.
It shows November 10.
This one shows November 1.
And we see it's from open graph meta tag.
I did like it.
And I think I don't need to actually define publication data.
So we can just remove it.
And I will just remove all right.
So remove, remove find publication date button because it's automatically showing.
And keep that in mind if I'm going to Chrome Web Store here.
The extension gallery cannot be scripted.
So I will probably have to add some sort of the icon.
So this is a notification and I will add a new agent.
Chrome extension have a notification type.
And right button corner and I want you to have notification date was found.
And when it wasn't in some galleries like this website that cannot be scripted.
And I can just paste up chart is notable.
So it's creating notification and in the meantime the modify Chrome extension was already added.
So remove the find publication date changes from the bottom.
I will wait for that and let me see the final result of this app.
So now what I'm going to do and we'll just go to extensions.
I will reload it.
And when it's reloaded, I see original data.
And here a publication.
So obviously if I pin it up and go to any website with me open this.
Okay, so we see that has access but doesn't show this URL pattern.
But if I use this.
Okay, we can go directly from here.
I can copy it.
I can mark it and we've read.
I can paste the image.
I have a data with this extension doesn't show any notification in my extension pin top.
It is now the possibility to see the snow publication data.
The problem is that if you go like solving.
It only shows when we click on an extension.
So the last feature we add, great.
It works now, but only when you press an extension.
I would like to check it upon loading a website.
So user will know if a data was found on this website.
Okay, when you visit in the website extension automatically checks for publication data.
That appears an extension icon within one or two seconds of page load.
I don't need to click the extension.
This is what I wanted.
So now I want to reload the extension.
I will reload it.
And now I will go here and open a few sites.
Just to see if it works.
So like a GitHub this one doesn't detect this one detect and this one detects as well.
Okay, this is the GitHub.
Let me find another one.
So people will know, okay, this is the Mark Zuckerberg.
Okay, it doesn't show.
And this is the, let's see, actually immediately in the metadata.
So it shows.
Okay, it works.
So it's nice and it just doesn't pop up again.
So only when the patch is like freshly load, it shows it.
The green.
Now I go here.
Airbus took off working press.
And we see it.
Okay, obviously we could like exchange it.
So this is the site.
But we didn't see when it was made and try to calculate how it was updated.
Go to any website and see like logs 2012.
And see actually what time was it he published.
So we can extend that extension, but I just wanted to show how we can create simple tools within
in the film minutes by using AI.